Ta-da!
First Nartao
So today's NARUTAO is
We've come to Tsukiji!
Yay!
I'm so happy!
Let's eat seafood! I want to eat seafood!
Today's NARUTAO walk is also called "NARUTAO walk".
I think this is the third time already!
Yes, at Tsukiji.
Asakusa vacant lot
If we include Asakusa, we've visited 4 places, right?
Yes, Tsukiji.
Tsukiji is also a famous eating spot.
I was looking forward to it.
I was looking forward to eating there, but...
I forgot my wallet today.
What?
I'm a cash man now.
Of course you are.
I'm a cash man.
I was in a bit of a rush to get out of the house and I forgot it.
I left my bag with my wallet in it.
So... today...
Can I borrow some money?
What should I do?
I'm sorry, please.
I'll pay you back later.
No problem.
I'll have fun.
I'm off!
Ta-da!
That's right.
I thought this was real, but it's a fake.
It's still strawberry candy, right?
Strawberry candy.
Right in front of you.
Bread.
When I was looking through it...
I found this.
Even for a bread lover like me.
It's great, isn't it?
You want to buy some? I'll get it.
I'd like to buy some.
Butter would be nice.
A croissant, please.
Yes, please.
Give me a petal.
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm sorry.
Okay, then.
Ta-da!
Patong.
Patron.
Croissant.
Croissant, croissant.
The police are after you.
Bon appétit.
Is it okay?
It's good.
It's good?
It's great.
It smells so good.
Bon appétit.
It's so buttery.
Yum! Yum!
Isn't it good?
What's it called? What's it called?
Yeah. Crunchy.
It's sticky.
It's light, so you can eat as many as you want.
Yeah, it's...
It's surprisingly big.
I thought we'd only need one for the two of us.
But we can have one of each.
It's a long day.
I'm still trying to eat a lot.
I have to keep my stomach open.
Yum!
Yes!
Croquette.
Delicious!
This croquette shop came up a lot!
I checked out Akatsuki Jiri.
So cute!
What's cute?
Well then...
Ponko's here.
Ponko alert!
Ponko alert.
Terra terra.
Let's eat!
Croquette!
Wow!
LOL!
I did a full-body impersonation!
LOL!LOL!
LOL!
Looks delicious.
Looks amazing!
dried bonito flakes
Hot!
So, Monjer, Meiji Monjer
Croquette! Meiji croquette!
Delicious! Let's eat!
It's huge!
It reminds me of munchi... Asakusa munchi for sure.
It's a croquette.
Right?
Ah!
Hot!
Hot hot hot!
They flew so fast, right?
They're really flying this way, aren't they?
But I'm sorry.
Oh, no.
How does it taste?
Hot.
It's a monger croquette, so it's got monger in it.
Oh, it's a monger.
It's just regular monger.
It's like there's a lot of monger in there.
How's it taste? Mentaiko!
But this is some kind of monja too.
Red!
Mentaiko on top?
Yes.
Piece by piece.
Mentaiko is delicious!
It's a novel way to make croquettes with monja.
I wonder how they do it.
Isn't it hard?
It's so sludgy!
I know what it is.
Like crab cream croquettes.
Oh! You're right, you're right, you're right, you're right.
It's like sludge.
That's what it looks like.
Delicious.
Oh!
What?
Hot!
Help me.
Are you okay?
I can't help you.
It's bad when it's hot.
Be careful when you eat it.
I want some.
Eggs.
Here.
One for the manager and one for me.
Wow, two.
Oh, my God.
It's like we're twins.
You're kidding? Oh, my God, it's true.
Yeah, they're stuck together.
I remember when we used to have ice cream.
This kind of ice cream?
Yeah, I think we used to have that.
Let's eat it.
Let's eat.
I'm going to eat an egg!
Let's eat!
Oh, yeah!
Is that steam?
Hey, it's warm!
Wow, it's like...
It's just like what I saw.
The one you saw.
Oh, wow.
Bon appétit.
Mm-hmm. Mm-hmm.
Mmm. Delicious.
Sweet.
I'm the one who lost.
It's sweet.
Happy.
Delicious.
It's the best!
Yellow color of 4!
It's the color.
He's holding an egg and saying four.
It's funny.
Four. Four.
Four.
Great!
Interesting.
Interesting
Mellow Mellow Mellow
Interestingamusing
Omoro (hereditary title; orig. one of the two highest such titles, later demoted to sixth highest rank)
Interesting
Amber
Strawberry candy
Bon appétit!
Strawberry
the bottom of the page
I look forward to working with you.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
I bought some strawberry candies.
Looks delicious!
Cheers!
Sounds good.
Mmm.
You okay?
Mm-hmm.
Mmm. - Mmm.
It's good.
It's delicious.
I even made my own candy strawberries at home.
You made candy strawberries?
He said he made them too.
His eyes are glazed over.
He made it all by himself.
Naru-ta-o!
Eat your candy strawberries.
I'm going to walk around some more.
I want some seafood.
I want to eat seafood!
But it's pretty much closed by now.
I thought so.
Maybe I came a little late.
It's better to come early.
I've been waiting a long time for coffee.
Neji Cafe.
Hey, how's today's coffee?
I haven't had my coffee today, so I thought it would be nice to have it now.
That's nice.
I didn't know coffee was a thing.
I thought...
I thought it would be nice if we had coffee.
There it is.
Seafood.
I'm going to go for a minute.
Oh!
Oh, my God!
Lemon.
I'll have some tea.
Wow, that looks good.
Oh, my God.
I've never had anything like this before.
Freshly made.
They were baking it right in front of me.
That's amazing!
Bon appétit!
Let's go, let's go, let's go!
Great!
Bon appétit!
Oh, my God! Wait, it's big!
It's hot!
Looks hot!
Okay, I'll get right to it.
Pre-prep!
Big scallops!
Bon appétit!
Yum!
So good!
So plump!
Your eyes are amazing.
I know it's got a lot of stuff in it, the scallops.
Butter, soy sauce, fried, so good!
So delicious!
Yes, that's why I'm done eating!
Thank you for the food!
I ate it all in one sitting!
Finally, it was just now!
And now I'm getting hungry...
I have one more place I want to go.
I saw some people walking around eating.
I saw a lot of people eating and walking around.
There are a lot of them.
I'd like to go there.
Yes!
Goal!
Surf's up!
Oh, soobeage!
I found it!
I love "Isobeage".
I'll have one too.
Oh, really?
Before we go to the restaurant we're looking for.
I didn't expect to stop by!
I'm going to eat!Let's eat!
Bon appétit!
Yum! Yum!
Delicious!
With cheese
It melts in your mouth.
He said Camembert cheese.
Nice bite.
Yeah!
It's overflowing.
Yum! Yum!
Amazing! Yummy.
I'll take it.
Yeah!
Yum! Yum!
Here it is!
Here we are!
Matcha latte.
Oh! Wow!
Many people had this!
This matcha latte.
It's absolutely delicious!
I want one! What! They have hojicha too!
What! They have hojicha too!
I want some! What! There's hojicha, too!
Really!
Even if there is, wow, I'm torn!
The soft-serve ice cream looks good too!
Oh! Looks so good! What should I do!
Happy worrying!
Thank you very much!
Bon appétit!
Matcha Latte, Matcha Above!
Yay!
Matcha iced latte
I had a double matcha iced latte!
Strong matcha green tea!
Now, let's drink it!
Bon appétit!
Delicious!
It's so thick!
It's good. It's good.
Delicious! I'm glad I got the double!
I heard that many matcha lovers make a double.
We both like matcha.
So we decided to have a double!
It's so thick!
Yeah, it's thick. They made it on the spot.
Yes, they made it on the spot.
The aroma is amazing.
It's amazing.
It's delicious.
It's so good!
NARUTAO Channel
So, we've been to Sukiyaki!
It was so much fun, wasn't it?
It was so much fun!
I think there are so many kinds of delicious food
There are so many different kinds of food.
It was late, so we only came in a couple of hours before the show.
If you're going to be there early, I think it's a good idea to go in the morning.
I guess morning is the best time to go, right?
That's for sure.
If we could come back when there's more abundance, I'd like to go back again.
I'd like to go again.
Well, that's all for now.
Bye bye!
See you soon!